yallwire.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy on Yallwire

Yallwire.com is a BLASTRO, INC. media site. All terms and policies for BLASTRO apply to Yallwire.com. At Yallwire, we are committed to protecting your privacy. The information we collect about you is used to provide you with a more personalized and richer experience while visiting our site. Please read further for details.

### How Does Yallwire Collect Information?

#### Your IP Address

Your IP address is a unique identifier we use to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Website tracking. We also use your IP address to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad, demographic information.

#### Cookies

Yallwire uses a feature on your Internet Web browser called a "cookie." A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your hard drive. It assigns a unique identification number to your computer and helps us maintain your preferences between visits to provide a personalized experience for you. Yallwire uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to tell us whether or not you have visited our Website before. We also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as anonymous session numbers, with them.

### What About Personal Information? Do You Collect That?

Yallwire does not house or collect any personal information about you unless you knowingly and willingly provide it.

#### Membership Registration

Yallwire has a registration process through which you voluntarily sign up to access the members-only features of our Website. During the registration process, we ask for your name, email address, and otherpersonal information. To make sure that nobody else can access our members-only features using your name or identity, we ask that you create a unique username with a password.

#### Newsletter Subscription

Yallwire sends one email newsletter a week which will include a list of our newest or top videos and a few featured news articles or contest updates. From time to time, we may also send an email notifying you of an upcoming contest or special features. You may opt out of receiving future mailings or cancel your subscription(s) at any time. We give you the choice whether to receive email or other contact from us and we give you the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving unwanted communications (click here for instructions.)

#### Contests and Promotions

When you enter a contest or take part in a promotion, we may ask for your name, mailing address and email address. Should a third party sponsor the contest or promotion, that party will have access to this information. We need this information in order to notify our winners and, when applicable, ship the winners' prizes..

### Does Yallwire Ever Share Information with Other Parties?

#### Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties

Yallwire may provide your email information to select partners, reputable companies or organizations whose products and services may interest you. If you prefer not to receive online marketing from Blastro, Inc., please contact us at contact@yallwire.com or call us at 1.512.485.3148. We do collect demographic and profile data, which is aggregated and shared with advertisers. Here's an example of what our advertisers would receive. "Of the 25,371 clicks your banner received, 38% of the those were by users between the ages of 25-34."

#### Links to Outside Third Parties

Yallwire may establish relationships with reputable business partners by creating a link between our sites. Yallwire chooses its business partners carefully. We are not, however, responsible for the content, maintenance or privacy policies of those sites. Once you click over to a third-party site, we encourage you to check their privacy policy. Users who click over to a third-party site from a link on Yallwire must be aware that Yallwire makes no warranties with regard to that site's policies or business practices. Yallwire is not responsible for any transactions that occur between the user and the third-party site. Should a user purchase any products or services from that third-party site, the user must contact the third-party site directly regarding any disputes that might occur, including, but notlimited to: delayed shipping, missing products, damaged goods, or pricing or billing discrepancies. Yallwire is not responsible for the actions of any third-party site.

#### Children's Guidelines

Yallwire does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children's Internet use. Also, we strongly encourage parents to help us enforce our privacy policy by instructing their children to never provide personal information on this site without permission.

#### Public Forums

Yallwire has on-demand streaming music videos, live streaming video programming, original on-demand streaming video, chat rooms, and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. As these forums are public and open for users to interact with each other,Yallwire expects all its users to respect the rights of others.

#### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visitsto this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

### Subscribe/Unsubscribe

Should you choose to in the future, Yallwire provides its users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us and our partners.

If you would like to cancel your registered membership, remove your information from our database and not receive future communications from us, please utilize one of the following options:

  * Email your request to [support@yallwire.com](mailto:support@yallwire.com)
  * Send your request via post to: 609 W. 18th #C, Austin, TX 78701

### Correct/Update

If you would like to change or modify information you previously provided to us, please utilize one of the following options:

  * Email your request to [contact@yallwire.com](mailto:contact@yallwire.com)
  * Send your request via post to: 609 W. 18th #C, Austin, TX 78701

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Website, you may contact: [info@yallwire.com](mailto:info@yallwire.com)
